<idea-plugin>
  <id>dev.vedhavyas.pure-black-github</id>
  <name>GitHub Dark Pure Black</name>
  <vendor email="7549475+vedhavyas@users.noreply.github.com" url="https://github.com/vedhavyas">Vedhavyas Singareddi</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
    <h3>GitHub Dark — Pure Black</h3>
    <p>A no-compromise pure black (<code>#000000</code>) variant of GitHub Dark for IntelliJ Platform IDEs. Built to feel like a TUI — flat, quiet, zero chrome tint.</p>
    <h4>What's pure black</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Editor pane, gutter, console, terminal</li>
      <li>All tool windows (Project view, Terminal, Services, Build, Run, Debug, Commit)</li>
      <li>Tab bar, main toolbar, status bar, popups, dialogs, menus</li>
      <li>Text fields, combo boxes, dropdowns</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>Visual separation</h4>
    <p>Subtle <code>#30363d</code> 1px borders between panels so you can tell them apart without sacrificing the flat black look. Uses GitHub Primer <code>border.default</code>.</p>
    <h4>Bundled bonuses (opt-in)</h4>
    <ul>
      <li><b>Keymap</b> — "Pure Black Mac" (Mac OS X with two tweaks: <code>Cmd+Enter</code> for Claude Code GUI chat newline, <code>Alt+N</code> for New Element menu)</li>
      <li><b>Code style</b> — "Pure Black Default" (language-standard indent: spaces everywhere, PEP 8 for Python, rustfmt for Rust, 2-space for HCL/Terraform/Protobuf/prototext)</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>First-run experience</h4>
    <p>On first install, a one-time notification offers to apply everything at once: the theme, editor color scheme, keymap, block cursor, indent guides off, intention bulb off. Click <b>Apply all</b> or <b>Dismiss</b>. Non-intrusive, never asks twice.</p>
    <h4>Parent</h4>
    <p>Extends IntelliJ's built-in Islands Dark. Fully compatible with the modern Islands UI.</p>
    <h4>Fonts</h4>
    <p>Bundled editor scheme references Fira Code. Install via <code>brew install --cask font-fira-code</code> on macOS. If not installed, IDEA falls back to another monospace.</p>
  ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <h4>1.2.9</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Warning and weak-warning ranges now show a dotted amber underline in the main editor, distinct from the error wave underline. Side error-stripe markers stay amber.</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.8</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Warning and weak-warning ranges no longer draw yellow outlines in the main editor; amber error-stripe markers stay visible on the side.</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.7</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Warning and weak-warning ranges no longer paint yellow blocks in the main editor; underline/effect and error-stripe markers stay amber.</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.6</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Apply all now disables IntelliJ's File Colors master toggle — no more green tint on test folders, grey on non-project files, etc. Matches the pure-black aesthetic. Folder role markers (excluded, generated) are unaffected.</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.5</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Fixed: Rust enum / type alias / macro-call / lifetime / trait-method tokens no longer inherit italic from the Rust plugin's Darcula overlay — explicit FONT_TYPE=0 on all org.rust.* overrides. Enum variants now render in constant blue, lifetimes in keyword coral.</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.4</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>De-branded for public release: keymap renamed "Pure Black Mac", code style renamed "Pure Black Default" (also reworked to language-standard defaults: spaces everywhere, PEP 8 Python, rustfmt Rust, 2-space HCL/Protobuf/prototext).</li>
      <li>Editor color scheme Rust token overrides realigned with authentic GitHub Dark: constants + static use the constant blue (`#79c0ff`) instead of the type purple; italics removed from enum / type alias / macro.</li>
      <li>First-run notification text rewritten to neutral wording.</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.3</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Fixed: first-run Apply all actually switches keymap to "Vedhavyas Mac" (bundledKeymap expects bare filename, registers by filename not XML name attribute — renamed resource accordingly)</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.1</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Fixed: first-run Apply all reliably switches editor scheme (direct getScheme(name) lookup + iterate-all fallback)</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.2.0</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Added first-run notification that applies all defaults in one click: theme, editor scheme, keymap, block cursor on, indent guides off, intention bulb off</li>
      <li>Persistent state — notification shows once, never again</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.1.0</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Added bundled keymap "Vedhavyas Mac"</li>
      <li>Added bundled code style "Vedhavyas Default"</li>
    </ul>
    <h4>1.0.0</h4>
    <ul>
      <li>Initial release — pure-black UI theme + editor color scheme + border accents</li>
    </ul>
  ]]></change-notes>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <themeProvider id="PURE_BLACK_GITHUB" path="/themes/pure-black-github.theme.json" />
    <bundledColorScheme path="/colors/github-dark-pure-black" />
    <bundledKeymap file="Pure Black Mac.xml" />
    <bundledCodeStyleSettings file="/codeStyles/PureBlackDefault.xml" />

    <notificationGroup id="PureBlackGithub" displayType="STICKY_BALLOON" />

    <applicationService serviceImplementation="dev.vedhavyas.pureblackgithub.FirstRunService" />
  </extensions>

  <applicationListeners>
    <listener class="dev.vedhavyas.pureblackgithub.FirstRunListener"
              topic="com.intellij.ide.AppLifecycleListener" />
  </applicationListeners>
</idea-plugin>
